<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Sonu Joshi</title>
    <link>https://sonu.tv/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Sonu Joshi</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 15:54:58 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sonu.tv/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Deploy Hugo on Github Pages With Travis CI</title>
      <link>https://sonu.tv/posts/deploy-hugo-on-github-pages-with-travis-ci/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 07 Jun 2018 15:54:58 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sonu.tv/posts/deploy-hugo-on-github-pages-with-travis-ci/</guid>
      <description>Getting started with Hugo is very interesting especially when you are new to static site generators. Just run hugo serve and your markdown files are converted into a website. But, when it comes deployment it&amp;rsquo;s really painful if you&amp;rsquo;re doing it manually and it&amp;rsquo;s more painful when you have to do the whole process all over again just to fix a stupid typo.
In my previous post - Setting Up Hugo on GitHub Pages, I talked about hosting Hugo sites on GitHub pages and one of the reason for doing so was Travis CI.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Setting Up Hugo on GitHub Pages</title>
      <link>https://sonu.tv/posts/setting-up-hugo-on-github-pages/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Jun 2018 22:39:12 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sonu.tv/posts/setting-up-hugo-on-github-pages/</guid>
      <description>Recently I started learning GoLang and came across Hugo which is an open source and the fastest static site generator. Before migrating to Hugo this blog was on self-hosted Ghost on DigitalOcean. Ghost is a minimal and straightforward blogging platform which is more into WordPress, Medium or Tumblr league because it comes with a really beautiful admin panel.
For shell lovers Jekyll, Hugo, Hexo and many other static site generators are no-nonsense tools for quickly spinning up &amp;ldquo;portfolio-cum-personal-blog&amp;rdquo; type websites.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>